let quizQuestions = [ // 23 questions
    {
        question: "What vehicle manufacturer has a logo with 4 interlocked rings?",
        questionOptions: [ "Audi", "Mercedes", "Volkswagen", "BMW"],
        correctAnswer: "Audi",
    },
    {
        question: "What a Mercedes Estate vehicles usually refered to as?",
        questionOptions: [ "Stretched", "Shooting Brake", "Coupe", "Anwesen"],
        correctAnswer: "Shooting Brake",
    },
    {
        question: "Which animal features in the logo for Lamborghini?",
        questionOptions: [ "Duck", "Bull", "Cow", "Bison"],
        correctAnswer: "Bull",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the original color for all Ferrari models?",
        questionOptions: [ "Red", "Yellow", "White", "Silver" ],
        correctAnswer: "Red",
    },
    {
        question: "Which iconic car manufacturer also made airplane engines?",
        questionOptions: [ "Aston Martin", "Ferrari", "Rolls Royce", "Mercedes" ],
        correctAnswer: "Rolls Royce",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the world’s all-time best selling car?",
        questionOptions: [ "Toyota Corolla", "Ford Fiesta", "Ford Focus", "Mini Cooper" ],
        correctAnswer: "Toyota Corolla",
    },
    {
        question: "In which year did Henry Ford establish the Ford Motor Company?",
        questionOptions: [ "1901", "1902", "1903", "1904"],
        correctAnswer: "1903",
    },
    {
        question: "Which sports car features in the Back To The Future trilogy?",
        questionOptions: [ "DeLorean", "Countach", "Testarossa", "DB6"],
        correctAnswer: "DeLorean",
    },
    {
        question: "What does Volkswagen mean?",
        questionOptions: [ "The People's Car", "Car of the People", "Car for the People", "The People's Best Car" ],
        correctAnswer: "The People's Car",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the best-selling electric car in history?",
        questionOptions: [ "Nissan Leaf", "Mercedes B-Class ED", "BMW i3", "Tesla Model 3"],
        correctAnswer: "Tesla Model 3",
    },
    {
        question: "Japanese car company Toyota was originally established as a textiles manufacturer. True or false?",
        questionOptions: [ "True", "False"],
        correctAnswer: "True",
    },
    {
        question: "Which race car is known as the widow maker?",
        questionOptions: [ "Porsche 917", "Porsche 918", "Porsche 911", "Porsche 991" ],
        correctAnswer: "Porsche 917",
    },
    {
        question: "What does BMW stand for?",
        questionOptions: [ "Belguim Motor Works", "Bavarian Motor Works", "Brazilian Motor Winners", "Bavarian Motor Winners" ],
        correctAnswer: "Bavarian Motor Works",
    },
    {
        question: "Which iconic car has appeared in seven Bond films, making its debut in the 1964 Goldfinger?",
        questionOptions: [ "Aston Martin DB5",  "Aston Martin DB6", "Aston Martin DB7", "Aston Martin DB9" ],
        correctAnswer: "Aston Martin DB5",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the 1984 Pontiac Trans Am, which co-stars with David Hasselhoff in Knight Rider?",
        questionOptions: [ "KITT", "KITE", "KIT", "KNIGHT" ],
        correctAnswer: "KITT",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the car driven by Mr Bean, the hapless character played by Rowan Atkinson?",
        questionOptions: [ "Ford", "Fiat", "Citroen", "Mini" ],
        correctAnswer: "Mini",
    },
    {
        question: "Who bought Rolls Royce in 1998?",
        questionOptions: [ "Mercedes", "BMW", "Volkswagen", "Ford" ],
        correctAnswer: "BMW",
    },
    {
        question: "Which was the first Bond film to star an Aston Martin?",
        questionOptions: [ "Dr. No", "From Russia with Love", "Goldfinger", "Thunderball" ],
        correctAnswer: "Goldfinger",
    },
    {
        question: "What type of feathers are used to brush the jaguars before they are painted to make sure they don’t attract dust?",
        questionOptions: [ "Emu", "Chicken", "Turkey", "Crow" ],
        correctAnswer: "Emu",
    },
    {
        question: "In what year was the Jaguar hood ornament removed from the front of the cars as a standard feature?",
        questionOptions: [ "2002", "2003", "2004", "2005" ],
        correctAnswer: "2005",
    },
    {
        question: "Where was the steering wheel of the first Land Rover?",
        questionOptions: [ "Middle", "Left", "Right", "Back" ],
        correctAnswer: "Middle",
    },
    {
        question: "MINI was the first manufacturer to make more room inside the car by doing what?",
        questionOptions: [ "Turn the engine sideways", "Put the engine in the back", "Remove the rear seats", "Remove the boot" ],
        correctAnswer: "Turn the engine sideways",
    },
    {
        question: "What colour was the Jaguar C-X75 that appears in the 2015 James Bond film Spectre?",
        questionOptions: [ "Green", "Blue", "Silver", "Orange" ],
        correctAnswer: "Orange",
    }
];